Guide to the Cindy Domingo Papers
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
Cindy Domingo papers
1973-2010
University of Washington Libraries Special Collections Box 352900 Seattle, WA 98195-2900
5651
Domingo, Cindy
43.9 cubic feet 44 boxes
Labor activist
Cindy Domingo, along with her brothers and sisters, played a key role in the Asian American and Filipino youth movements of the 1970s, and has been a community leader in the Seattle area since then. In the 1970s, she helped lead solidarity campaigns on the University of Washington campus against the Marcos dictatorship in the Philippines. She was active in the Union of Democratic Filipinos (KDP), for which she did organizing in Seattle and Oakland. On June 1st, 1981, Cindy's brother Silme Domingo, a KDP organizer and union reform activist in ILWU Local 37, was assassinated along with fellow union leader Gene Viernes. For the next ten years, Cindy served as the National Chair for the Committee for Justice for Domingo and Viernes. The campaign resulted in the conviction of the former ILWU Local 37 President and family friend Tony Baruso for organizing the assassination, and also proved that the murders had been ordered by the Marcos regime with U.S. government knowledge.
Cindy Domingo was an active member of the Washington State Rainbow Coalition in the 1980s, and served on the boards of the Church Council of Greater Seattle, LELO, and the International Examiner. She has been Board President of the Center for Social Justice and co-chair of U.S. Women & Cuba Collaboration, and currently serves as the Legislative Aide to King County Councilmember Larry Gossett.
Arranged in 3 accessions:
Accession no. 5651-001, Cindy Domingo papers, 1978-2010
Accession no. 5651-002, Cindy Domingo papers, 1982-1992
Accession no. 5651-003, Cindy Domingo papers, 1973-2009
Records relating to Cindy's activism and work as an officer in several organizations including Committee for Justice for Domingo and Viernes, Line of March, and the Union of Democratic Filipinos (In Tagalog: Katipunan ng mga Demokratikong Pilipino), or KDP.
Open to all users.
Domingo, Cindy$vArchives; Political activists$zWashington (State)$zSeattle$vArchives; Human rights workers$zWashington (State)$zSeattle$vArchives; Labor$zWashington (State)$xHistory$vSources; Labor$zPhilippines$xHistory$vSources; Labor unions$zWashington (State)$xHistory$vSources; Labor movement$zWashington (State)$xHistory$vSources; Labor movement$zPhilippines$xHistory$vSources; Women's rights$zWashington (State)$xHistory$vSources; Filipino Americans$xHistory$vSources; Human rights$xHistory$vSources; Philippines$xHistory$y1946-1986$vSources; Philippines$xHistory$y1986-$vSources; Political campaigns$zWashington (State)$xHistory$vSources; Newsletters; Press releases; Business correspondence; Ephemera; Minutes (Records); Records (Documents); Photographs; Legal documents; Financial records; Newspaper clippings; Labor Archives of Washington (University of Washington); Personal Papers/Corporate Records; Labor History; Labor Unions; International Relations
- Cindy Domingo papers, 1978-2010; 5651-001; 18.92 cubic feet 19 boxes
  Materials related to Cindy Domingo's activism and involvement with the Committee for Justice for Domingo and Viernes as well as the KDP.
  Open to all users.
  Cindy Domingo 9/2/2011.
  - CINDY DOMINGO PAPERS, SERIES I (Box-folder Box 1-Box 19)
    - Events Seattle, 1981-1989 (Box-folder 1/1)
    - Check Register, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 1/2)
    - Youth Project Account- Old Checks, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 1/3)
    - Rent, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 1/4)
    - Monthly Financial Reports, 1983 (Box-folder 1/5)
    - Finance Reports - Seattle, 1982 (Box-folder 1/6)
    - Receipts - Seattle Account, 1983 (Box-folder 1/7)
    - Sprint- Phone, 1983 (Box-folder 1/8)
    - Tax/Incorporation Forms for Committee for Justice for Domingo and Viernes, 1979-1983 (Box-folder 1/9)
    - Expense Receipt- Leni, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 1/10)
    - Expense Receipt- Grace, 1983 (Box-folder 1/11)
    - Expense Receipt- Susan, 1983 (Box-folder 1/12)
    - Other Bills - Paid, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 1/13)
    - Fundraising General Information, 1985 (Box-folder 1/14)
    - Dollars for Change Silent & Live Auction materials, 1992 (Box-folder 1/15)
    - Direct Mail Samples, 1982-1989 (Box-folder 1/16)
    - Direct Mail Campaign, 1989 (Box-folder 1/17)
    - Direct Mail General Information, 1980 (Box-folder 1/18)
    - Direct Mail Campaign 8/89, 1989-1992 (Box-folder 1/19)
    - Direct Mail Seattle 8/82, 1982 (Box-folder 1/20)
    - Brocka Film Fundraiser, 1988 (Box-folder 1/21)
    - Christic Institute Fundraiser 5/88, 1988 (Box-folder 1/22)
    - Flyers for Event: Political Assassination in Seattle, Jazz for Justice, 1982 (Box-folder 1/23)
    - Griener, Lynn, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 1/24)
    - National Staff Training Session, 1983 (Box-folder 1/25)
    - Plans Seattle, 1989 (Box-folder 1/26)
    - Youth Project Monthly Report 1986, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 1/27)
    - Youth Project Monthly Report 1984-1985, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 1/28)
    - Youth Project Correspondence, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 1/29)
    - Youth Project Monthly Report 1987, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 1/30)
    - Church Council of Greater Seattle Check Request Forms 1990, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 1/31)
    - Church Council of Greater Seattle Check Request Forms 1988, 1988-1991 (Box-folder 1/32)
    - Church Council of Greater Seattle Monthly Reports 1990, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 1/33)
    - Church Council of Greater Seattle Account Balance Sheets, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 1/34)
    - Church Council of Greater Seattle Check Request Forms, 1989 (Box-folder 1/35)
    - Commonwealth Fund, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 1/36)
    - CAMP 25th Anniversary, 1982-1991 (Box-folder 1/37)
    - C.S. Fund, 1959-1989 (Box-folder 1/38)
    - Ferry, W.H. & Carol, 1985-1990 (Box-folder 1/39)
    - Church Council of Greater Seattle Check Request Forms 1988, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 1/40)
    - Samuel Rubin Foundation, 1986-1990 (Box-folder 2/1)
    - Vanguard Foundation, 1983-1990 (Box-folder 2/2)
    - Pacific Peace Fund, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 2/3)
    - Labor & Employment Legal Office, 1973-1987 (Box-folder 2/4)
    - MacArthur Foundation, 1986-1990 (Box-folder 2/5)
    - First Interstate Bank Receipts, 1987-1994 (Box-folder 2/6)
    - First Interstate Bank Monthly Statement 1990, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 2/7)
    - First Interstate Bank Monthly Statement 1989 (Box-folder 2/8)
    - First Interstate Bank Bank Statements 1988 (Box-folder 2/9)
    - First Interstate Bank Account Receipts, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 2/10)
    - First Interstate Account Receipts - 1988, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 2/11)
    - First Interstate Account Receipts - 1986, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 2/12)
    - Legal Account Receipts, 1986 (Box-folder 2/13)
    - Deposits, Undated (Box-folder 2/14)
    - Contributions, 1989 (Box-folder 2/15)
    - In-Kind Donations, 1983 (Box-folder 2/16)
    - North Shore Unitarian Universalist Veatch Program, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 2/17)
    - Playboy Foundation, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 2/18)
    - Presbyterian Church, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 2/19)
    - Tides Foundation, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 2/20)
    - Funds, 1980-1989 (Box-folder 2/21)
    - Foundations Correspondence, 1981-1989 (Box-folder 2/22)
    - Proposals, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 2/23)
    - Direct Mail 89, 1986-1990 (Box-folder 2/24)
    - CAPP Street Foundation, 1987 (Box-folder 2/25)
    - Rainier Bank Account Bank Statements/Checks, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 2/26)
    - First Interstate Bank Bank Statements/Checks, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 2/27)
    - Marcos Regime on Trial Pamphlets, c. 1980s-c. 1990s (Box-folder 2/28)
    - Registers, Notebook, etc..., 1982-1987 (Box-folder 2/29)
    - Accounting-Committee for Justice for Domingo and Viernes (CJDV), 1989-1991 (Box-folder 2/30)
    - Unpublished Manuscript for Brothers and Sisters a novel by Thomas Churchill, c. 1980s (Box-folder 2/31)
    - Manuscript, pp. 170-227, c. 1980s (Box-folder 2/32)
    - Manuscript, pp. 109-239, c. 1980s (Box-folder 2/33)
    - Revisions, Tom Churchill, 1990 (Box-folder 2/34)
    - Synopsis of the complaint in Domingo v. Marcos, c. 1980s (Box-folder 2/35)
    - Committee for Justice for Domingo and Viernes (CJDV) letters, 1989 (Box-folder 2/36)
    - Seattle Times/ January 29, 1992 (Box-folder 2/37)
    - Committee for Justice for Domingo and Viernes (CJDV): Press Clippings, 1982-1989 (Box-folder 2/38)
    - Press Clippings (1), 1985-1990 (Box-folder 2/39)
    - Press Clippings (2), 1986-1990 (Box-folder 3/1)
    - Committee for Justice for Domingo and Viernes (CJDV): Press Clippings, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 3/2)
    - Committee for Justice for Domingo and Viernes (CJDV): Media Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 3/3)
    - Committee for Justice for Domingo and Viernes (CJDV): Media Logs, 1989 (Box-folder 3/4)
    - Committee for Justice for Domingo and Viernes (CJDV): Corespondence (non-media), 1989 (Box-folder 3/5)
    - Committee for Justice for Domingo and Viernes (CJDV) Press Release, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 3/6)
    - Committee for Justice for Domingo and Viernes (CJDV): Newsletters/Flyers, 1989 (Box-folder 3/7)
    - Committee for Justice for Domingo and Viernes (CJDV): Caughlin Event, 1989 (Box-folder 3/8)
    - Committee for Justice for Domingo and Viernes (CJDV): Media Lists, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 3/9)
    - Black graphic of text: MARCOS REGIME ON TRIAL, Undated (Box-folder 3/10)
    - Committee for Justice for Domingo and Viernes (CJDV): Direct Mail Art Devt., 1989 (Box-folder 3/11)
    - Committee for Justice for Domingo and Viernes (CJDV): New Letterhead, c. 1980s (Box-folder 3/12)
    - New Brochure, 1989 (Box-folder 3/13)
    - Committee for Justice for Domingo and Viernes (CJDV): Funding Exchange, 1990 (Box-folder 3/14)
    - Additional News Clippings, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 3/15)
    - Committee for Justice for Domingo and Viernes (CJDV): Test Mailings, 1989 (Box-folder 3/16)
    - Kozu- King $100, 1989 (Box-folder 3/17)
    - Committee for Justice for Domingo and Viernes (CJDV): Informed $100, 1989 (Box-folder 3/18)
    - Committee for Justice for Domingo and Viernes (CJDV) Letter: Existing, 1989 (Box-folder 3/19)
    - Christic Letter + List, 1989 (Box-folder 3/20)
    - Caughlin List, c. 1989 (Box-folder 3/21)
    - Committee for Justice for Domingo and Viernes (CJDV) Existing $100 Mailing List, 1989 (Box-folder 3/22)
    - Caughlin Letter, 1989 (Box-folder 3/23)
    - National Asian American Bar Association List, 1988 (Box-folder 3/24)
    - ALA Letter- Melendez, 1989 (Box-folder 3/25)
    - Committee for Justice for Domingo and Viernes (CJDV): FR Appeal Letters- Old, 1988 (Box-folder 3/26)
    - Committee for Justice for Domingo and Viernes (CJDV) Donors, 1989 (Box-folder 3/27)
    - Committee for Justice for Domingo and Viernes (CJDV) Brochure (Help Bring Ferdinand Marcos to Trial), c. 1980s-c. 1990s (Box-folder 3/28)
    - Labor and Employment Law Office (LELO): Annual Event 2001, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 3/29)
    - 2002 Annual Event Labor and Employment Law Office (LELO), 2001-2002 (Box-folder 3/30)
    - Annual Event Labor and Employment Law Office (LELO) 2001 (Box-folder 3/31)
    - Annual Event Labor and Employment Law Office (LELO) 2000 (Box-folder 3/32)
    - 2002 Annual Labor and Employment Law Office (LELO) Giving Campaign (Box-folder 3/33)
    - 2000 Annual Giving Campaign (Box-folder 3/34)
    - Anti-War, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 3/35)
    - Stamp, 1989 (Box-folder 3/36)
    - National Anti War Meeting, 2002 (Box-folder 4/1)
    - Asian American Labor, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 4/2)
    - Asian Pacific American Report Violence Against, 1998 (Box-folder 4/3)
    - Board Meetings 2002 (Box-folder 4/4)
    - Board Meetings 2001 (Box-folder 4/5)
    - A Territory Resource, 2001 (Box-folder 4/6)
    - Board Meetings 2000 (Box-folder 4/7)
    - Family Wage Jobs (1 of 2), 1996-2001 (Box-folder 4/8)
    - Family Wage Jobs (2 of 2), 1998-1999 (Box-folder 4/9)
    - Sexual Exploitation- Women & Children, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 4/10)
    - Sweatshops, 1992-1999 (Box-folder 4/11)
    - United Nation Conference on Racism, 2001 (Box-folder 4/12)
    - Wards Cove, 1991-2001 (Box-folder 4/13)
    - Wards Cove 2001, 2000-2002 (Box-folder 4/14)
    - Organization of Chinese Americans, 2001 (Box-folder 4/15)
    - Labor and Employment Law Office, 1998-2001 (Box-folder 4/16)
    - Articles, 2001- (Box-folder 4/17)
    - Human RIghts Booklets published by The People's Decade for Human Rights Education (PDHRE), c. 1990s (Box-folder 4/18)
    - 2nd half of Dissertation, 2001 (Box-folder 4/19)
    - Summit, 2001 (Box-folder 4/20)
    - Background Materials, 1991-2001 (Box-folder 4/21)
    - Ward Cove Legal Papers, 1999 (Box-folder 4/22)
    - Wards Cove Resolutions, 1972-2001 (Box-folder 4/23)
    - Wards Cove Bill (1993) (Box-folder 4/24)
    - Workers Voices Coalition, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 4/25)
    - Women of Color in Labor Conference, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 4/26)
    - Workers Center/Labor and Employment Law Office (LELO) Projects, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 5/1)
    - Withey's Case, 2000 (Box-folder 5/2)
    - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom (WILPF) Membership Pamphlets, 1985 (Box-folder 5/3)
    - WILPF Newsletters, 1998-2004 (Box-folder 5/4)
    - Jane Adams Book Awards, 2004 (Box-folder 5/5)
    - Justice for Ward's Cove Cannery Posters, 1994 (Box-folder 5/6)
    - WILPF Information, 1997-2000 (Box-folder 5/7)
    - WILPF Congress, 1983-2002 (Box-folder 5/8)
    - Asia-Pacific/Morikawa Conference Task Force (APMCTF)- Church Council of Greater Seattle (CCGS), 1993-1996 (Box-folder 5/9)
    - PRTF, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 5/10)
    - Seattle Times Strike, 2000 (Box-folder 5/11)
    - Newsletter- Labor and Employment Law Office (LELO), 1998-2002 (Box-folder 5/12)
    - National Asian Pacific American Women's Forum (NAPAWF), 1998-2002 (Box-folder 5/13)
    - Mindinao/Phil Forum 11/00, 2000 (Box-folder 5/14)
    - Prison Industrial Complex, 2000 (Box-folder 5/15)
    - Port Campaign, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 5/16)
    - Reclaim Democracy, 2002 (Box-folder 5/17)
    - Relicensing Program, 1999-2002 (Box-folder 5/18)
    - Seabeck Conference, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 5/19)
    - New Voices, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 5/20)
    - Party Building, 2002 (Box-folder 5/21)
    - Port of Seattle Issue, 1996-2002 (Box-folder 5/22)
    - Mexico Conference 7/99, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 5/23)
    - Links on the Chain, 1999 (Box-folder 5/24)
    - Board Retreat 2000, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 5/25)
    - National Federation of Filipino American Associations (NaFFAA), 2000 (Box-folder 5/26)
    - Filipino Veterans, 2000 (Box-folder 6/1)
    - Fiscal Policies- Northwest Labor and Employment Law Office (LELO), 2000 (Box-folder 6/2)
    - Media Coverage- Labor and Employment Law Office (LELO), 1999-2002 (Box-folder 6/3)
    - Mailing List- Labor and Employment Law Office (LELO), 2001 (Box-folder 6/4)
    - KDP Reunion, 2001 (Box-folder 6/5)
    - International Worker to Worker Newsletter, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 6/6)
    - Labor Left, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 6/7)
    - Funding Proposals, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 6/8)
    - Hedgebrook, 2002 (Box-folder 6/9)
    - Caughlan Award, 2001 (Box-folder 6/10)
    - Church Council of Greater Seattle (CCGS) Board Meeting, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 6/11)
    - Cordova, Fred, 2000 (Box-folder 6/12)
    - Correspondence 2001 (Box-folder 6/13)
    - Executive Committee 2001, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 6/14)
    - Immigration Issue Information, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 6/15)
    - International Examiner, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 6/16)
    - Board Mini Retreat 2002 (Box-folder 6/17)
    - Board Retreat 2001, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 6/18)
    - Executive Meeting 2000 (Box-folder 6/19)
    - Executive Meeting 1999-1998, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 6/20)
    - Events- Labor and Employment Law Office (LELO) Sponsored, 2002 (Box-folder 6/21)
    - Building Blocks, 2000 (Box-folder 6/22)
    - By-Laws/Labor and Employment Law Office (LELO), 1973 (Box-folder 6/23)
    - Board Meetings 1997-1999 (Box-folder 6/24)
    - Board Retreat 1998, 1989-1998 (Box-folder 6/25)
    - Labor and Employment Law Office (LELO) Spheres, 2000-2002 (Box-folder 6/26)
    - Board Retreat 1999, 1999-2002 (Box-folder 6/27)
    - Labor and Employment Law Office (LELO) Projects 2002 (Box-folder 6/28)
    - 2002 LELO Retreat, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 6/29)
    - LELO Reports, 1997 (Box-folder 6/30)
    - Speaking Engagments-Cindy Domingo, 1995-1998 (Box-folder 6/31)
    - Speaking Engagments, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 6/32)
    - Copy of News Article by Dean Wong (New national organization seeks to empower API women) regarding the Asian Pacfic Women's Leadership Institute, 1995 (Box-folder 6/33)
    - United States Committments, 1995 (Box-folder 6/34)
    - American Women's Roundtable, 1996 (Box-folder 6/35)
    - Basecamp, 1995 (Box-folder 6/36)
    - Copy of News Article from The Daily of the University of Washington: UW Burma Action Group joins in Protest by Alysha Webb, c. 1990s (Box-folder 6/37)
    - Cate, Jan Thesis, 1991 (Box-folder 6/38)
    - Chung, Dr., 1995-1997 (Box-folder 6/39)
    - Comfort Women, 1996 (Box-folder 6/40)
    - Conference 8/1996 (Box-folder 6/41)
    - Everywoman's Conference 11/18/95, 1995 (Box-folder 6/42)
    - Everywoman's Conference-, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 6/43)
    - Delegation Meetings, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 7/1)
    - Disarmament Coalition, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 7/2)
    - Donations-Receipts, 1995 (Box-folder 7/3)
    - Everywoman's Delegation Information, 1995 (Box-folder 7/4)
    - Financial Reports- Institute for Global Security Studies (IGSS), 1995-1997 (Box-folder 7/5)
    - French Nuclear Testing, 1995 (Box-folder 7/6)
    - Funding Requests, 1995 (Box-folder 7/7)
    - Gabriela, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 7/8)
    - Copy of News Article: Fear and female genital mutilation, 1996 (Box-folder 7/9)
    - Global Fund for Women, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 7/10)
    - Mail Lists, 1996 (Box-folder 7/11)
    - Newspaper Clippings- Everywoman's Delegation, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 7/12)
    - Newspaper Clippings- Miscellanous, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 7/13)
    - NGO Application, 1995 (Box-folder 7/14)
    - Northwest Women's Insitute, 1995 (Box-folder 7/15)
    - Okinawa, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 7/16)
    - Sex Trafficking, 1994-1997 (Box-folder 7/17)
    - Economic Development Opinionaire, 1995 (Box-folder 7/18)
    - Spady Newspaper- 1995 Conference (Box-folder 7/19)
    - Opinionaire, 1995 (Box-folder 7/20)
    - Everywoman's Delegation Letterhead, c. 1995 (Box-folder 7/21)
    - War Crimes, 1997 (Box-folder 7/22)
    - Women in Black, 1996 (Box-folder 7/23)
    - Women's Building Materials, Undated (Box-folder 7/24)
    - Women of Color Resource Center, 1996 (Box-folder 7/25)
    - Working Women Campaign, 1997 (Box-folder 7/26)
    - Email Correspondence (1/3), 1996 (Box-folder 7/27)
    - Email Correspondence (2/3), 1995 (Box-folder 7/28)
    - Email Correspondence (3/3), 1995-1996 (Box-folder 7/29)
    - Email Correspondence, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 7/30)
    - Miscellanous Women's Employment Materials, 1993-1997 (Box-folder 7/31)
    - Filipino Veterans, 1997 (Box-folder 7/32)
    - Igorota- The Displacement of Women from Ancestral Land, 1988 (Box-folder 7/33)
    - Opinionaire- Sorted/Not Sorted, 1997 (Box-folder 7/34)
    - Advance Unedited Draft re; Fourth World Conference on Women, 1995 (Box-folder 7/35)
    - Email Correspondence (4), 1995 (Box-folder 7/36)
    - Email Correspondence (3), 1995 (Box-folder 8/1)
    - Email Correspondence (2), 1995 (Box-folder 8/2)
    - Email Correspondence (1), 1995 (Box-folder 8/3)
    - Women's Testimonies from Kashmir, 1994 (Box-folder 8/4)
    - Working Women in Japan, 1995 (Box-folder 8/5)
    - Technological Changes & Women's Employment in Asia, 1995 (Box-folder 8/6)
    - NGO Forum on Women, Beijing '95, 1995 (Box-folder 8/7)
    - Institute for Global Security: Women of the Pacific, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 8/8)
    - Miscellaneous publications, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 8/9)
    - Forum of Democratic Leaders in the Asia-Pacific handbook, 1994 (Box-folder 8/10)
    - Refugee Women, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 8/11)
    - Women's World Banking, 1995 (Box-folder 8/12)
    - Women of Asia, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 8/13)
    - Filipino Women, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 8/14)
    - NGO Forum Report by Women Workers' group, 1995 (Box-folder 8/15)
    - Women's NGO Coalition Newsletter, 1995 (Box-folder 8/16)
    - Austrialia, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 8/17)
    - Women of Vietnam, 1995 (Box-folder 8/18)
    - Indonesian Women Workers, 1995 (Box-folder 8/19)
    - Directory/Catalog, 1995 (Box-folder 8/20)
    - The Tribune, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 8/21)
    - Forum '95, 1995 (Box-folder 8/22)
    - Condemn Sexual-Apartheid in Iran, 1995 (Box-folder 8/23)
    - Korea, 1988-1992 (Box-folder 9/1)
    - Japan, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 9/2)
    - Fiji, 1987 (Box-folder 9/3)
    - France, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 9/4)
    - General Information, 1986-1990 (Box-folder 9/5)
    - Hawaii, 1989 (Box-folder 9/6)
    - Marshall Islands, 1986-1990 (Box-folder 9/7)
    - Pacific Campagin to Disarm the Seas, 1988-1991 (Box-folder 9/8)
    - Pacific Vision WILPF Publication, 1988-1994 (Box-folder 9/9)
    - Pacific Ecumenical Forum, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 9/10)
    - New California, 1989 (Box-folder 9/11)
    - Palau, 1987 (Box-folder 9/12)
    - Resources/Organizations/Publications, 1988-1991 (Box-folder 9/13)
    - Taiwan, 1988 (Box-folder 9/14)
    - Voices of Hope and Anger 4/89, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 9/15)
    - Vietnam/Cambodia, 1988-1992 (Box-folder 9/16)
    - Philippines Political Affair, 1987-1992 (Box-folder 9/17)
    - Civil Rights Report, February 1992 (Box-folder 9/18)
    - Outreach/Marcos Visit Campaign, 1987-1991 (Box-folder 9/19)
    - Letter Writing Campaign+miscellaneous, 1988-1992 (Box-folder 9/20)
    - Philippine Report, 1980-1986 (Box-folder 9/21)
    - Philippine Labor Alert+Philippine Witness, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 9/22)
    - Making An Impact/Asian Pacific American Labor Alliance/April 30-May 2, 1992 (Box-folder 9/23)
    - International Solidarity News Digest, 1986-1992 (Box-folder 9/24)
    - Donations, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 9/25)
    - Ecotrust, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 9/26)
    - LELO Board Meetings, 1987-1993 (Box-folder 9/27)
    - Stationary, Undated (Box-folder 9/28)
    - IRS, 1993 (Box-folder 9/29)
    - Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 9/30)
    - ACWA Lawsuits, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 9/31)
    - Press Statements Organizations/Individuals, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 9/32)
    - Award- LELO, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 9/33)
    - Mailing List, 1991 (Box-folder 9/34)
    - Updates, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 9/35)
    - Resolutions, 1992 (Box-folder 9/36)
    - Ward Cove Responses, 1990 (Box-folder 9/37)
    - Press Statements Congressional Representatives, 1989-1992 (Box-folder 9/38)
    - Mailing Lists, 1987-1991 (Box-folder 9/39)
    - Asian American Mailing Lists, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 10/1)
    - Petitions- Copies, 1992 (Box-folder 10/2)
    - Press Articles, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 10/3)
    - Ward Cove Workers Act, 1993 (Box-folder 10/4)
    - Justice for Wards Cove Workers Act Press Packet, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 10/5)
    - National Asian Pacific American Bar Association (NAPABA), 1991 (Box-folder 10/6)
    - Lowry Fundraiser, 1992 (Box-folder 10/7)
    - Letters to Editors, 1991 (Box-folder 10/8)
    - Legal Briefs- Ninth Circuit Appeal, 1988-1991 (Box-folder 10/9)
    - Mailing List- Congress, 1992 (Box-folder 10/10)
    - Mailing List- LELO, c. 1990s (Box-folder 10/11)
    - Media Coverage, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 10/12)
    - Media List National, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 10/13)
    - Media Packets, 1991 (Box-folder 10/14)
    - Legal Briefs- Ninth Circuit Appeal (1 of 2), 1991 (Box-folder 10/15)
    - Legal Briefs- Ninth Circuit Appeal (2 of 2), 1988-1991 (Box-folder 10/16)
    - Asian Pacific American Labor Alliance (APALA), 1991-1993 (Box-folder 10/17)